bdjobstotal.com 2017-06-20

# Privacy&Policy - bdjobstotal.com

**Privacy Policy**

Bdjobstotal

Privacy Policy for [http://bdjobstotal.com](http://bdjobstotal.com/)  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at http://bdjobstotal.com  
privacy-policy. At [http://bdjobstotal.com](http://bdjobstotal.com/) we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by [http://bdjobstotal.com](http://bdjobstotal.com/) and how we use it.  
Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, [http://bdjobstotal.com](http://bdjobstotal.com/) makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services analytic. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable Cookies and Web Beacons  
[http://bdjobstotal.com](http://bdjobstotal.com/) uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  
Double Click DART Cookie  
? Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [http://bdjobstotal.com](http://bdjobstotal.com/)  
? Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to [http://bdjobstotal.com](http://bdjobstotal.com/) and other sites on the Internet.  
? Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Our Advertising Partners  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….  
While each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site, an updated and hyperlinked resource is maintained here: Privacy Policies. You may consult this listing to find the privacy policy for each of the advertising partners of http://bdjobstotal.com  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on http://bdjobstotal.com and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also  
be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.  
http://bdjobstotal.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
